<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
	<properties>
		<title>Welcome</title>
		<author email="greg.case@apexit.com">Greg Case</author>
	</properties>
	<body>
		<section name="Welcome to Charm">
			<p>Charm is the next generation framework being developed by ApexIT</p>
			<subsection name="About Charm">
				<p>
				Charm is Apex's 3rd generation framework for developing standards-based internet applications.
				Leveraging our experience with our iFrame and iFrame2 frameworks (currently the foundation for scores 
				of applications used by hundreds of thousands of people everyday and managing billions of dollars 
				in assets and transactions) we set out to design our new framework on a select set of open source technologies.
			</p>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="Design Goals">
			<p>
			The goal of Charm is basically the same as the goal of all of Apex's past framework development: to make it faster and easier for us to 
			create more robust and sophisticated applications for our clients. Specifically, the goal is to:
			</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Avoid reinventing the wheel</li>
					<li>Enhance our ability to support our clients by leveraging a common architecture</li>
					<li>Reduce the time spent writing tedious code, freeing up time to solve unique business problems</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="User's Guide">
				<p>
			Look at all of this swell documentation!
			</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i>
							<a href="getting_started.html">Getting Started</a>
						</i>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i>
							<a href="configuration.html">Configuring Charm</a>
						</i>
					</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="Developing Charm">
				<p>
			There is plenty of work to be done. If you are interested in getting involved, the following may help:
			</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i>How can I
              <a href="about.html#get-involved">get involved</a>?
            </i>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i>What <a href="docs_required.html">documentation is needed</a>?
					</i>
					</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="Selling Charm">
				<p>
			This section would contain a list of documents to be used for the sales team when touting the advantages of charm.
			</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fast Development</li>
					<li>Standards Based</li>
					<li>Query Isolation</li>
					<li>Service Oriented</li>
					<li>Probably does not cause cancer</li>
				</ul>
			</subsection>
		</section>
	</body>
</document>
